Jackson Congdon

Profile

Computer science undergraduate with 15 years' experience in customer service and the previous 3 years' work in sales environments. Transitioning to career in IT and computer science while finishing B.S. in Computer Science. Consistently recognized with 5 star client ratings at Hancock Whitney and "Employee of the Month" award at Diabetes Management & Supplies. Experienced with Microsoft Windows, Microsoft Office, Mac OS X, and Linux.

Education

Western Governors University Bachelor of Science, Computer Science Scheduled Graduation Sep. 2022

Completed coursework includes: Network & Security Foundations (OSI model, setup and maintenance of wired and wireless networks, TCP/IP, DNS, DHCP, VPNs, security, firewalls, routers, switches, virtualization) |

Data Management Foundations & Applications (SQL, data modeling, normalization) | Scripting & Programming Applications (C++) | Computer architecture | Introduction to IT | Fundamentals of Information Security | Web Development Foundations | Discrete Mathematics I | Calculus I

Experience

Harahan, LA
Multi Service Banker
June 2019 – Present
Teller
Nov. 2018 – May 2019

- Resolved customer technical support issues with online banking
- Point of contact at branch for IT department to troubleshoot and resolve issues remotely
- Created daily report for Financial Center Manager of accounts with significant balance changes
- Partnered with Financial Advisor to refer clients to Investment Services for investing, loans and other banking services

Diabetes Management & Supplies
New Accounts Sales Manager
Existing Accounts & New Accounts Team Lead
Existing Accounts & New Accounts Sales Representative

Harahan, LA April 2018 – Oct. 2018 Aug. 2017 – March 2018 Jan. 2017 – July 2017

- Spoke with patients requiring escalation to solve customer service and health insurance related concerns
- Used Excel to automate tasks, improve sales reporting, and build solutions to challenges created by new partners
- Created email, texting, and mailing based marketing strategies to capture new leads and maximize current patients
- Created daily, weekly and monthly sales reports to track individual goals and department budgets
- Developed relationships with manufacturing partners and worked with manufacturers' nationwide sales teams

Lilette Restaurant	Server	New Orleans, LA	Jan. 2012 – July 2012, Sep. 2015 – Dec. 2016
Atchafalaya Restaurant	Server	New Orleans, LA	May 2015 – Aug. 2016
Tuscany Restaurant	Server	Chicago, IL	July 2012 – May 2015
The Ritz-Carlton	Server	New Orleans, LA	Feb. 2011 – Dec. 2011

Six Flags Great America
Senior Supervisor, Customer Service
Supervisor, Customer Service & Admissions
Team Lead, Admissions
Team Member, Admissions

Gurnee, IL Jan. 2009 – Jan. 2011 March 2007 – Dec. 2008 July 2005 – Feb. 2007 April 2005 – June 2005

- Handled any guests who had exhausted options with Customer Service Team Members
- Attended daily Park Communication meetings and oversaw all supervisors, team leads, and team members
- Created and presented department training seminars for new hires and current employees
- Facilitated long term development of team members from entry level to supervisory positions